{
    "subject": "resource/The_King_of_Fighters_'95",
    "predicate": "ontology/computingPlatform",
    "object": "resource/Neo_Geo_CD",
    "human_readable": "The King of Fighters '95 was played on Neo Geo CD.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9609830975532532,
            "question": "Are there other games besides The King of Fighters '95 that were played on Neo Geo CD?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9158195853233337,
            "question": "What other games were released on Neo Geo CD around the same time as The King of Fighters '95?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8513132929801941,
            "question": "On what platform was The King of Fighters '95 played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7788782715797424,
            "question": "Is The King of Fighters '95 a fighting game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6965059041976929,
            "question": "Was The King of Fighters '95 a popular game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.683668851852417,
            "question": "Who developed The King of Fighters '95?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5549260973930359,
            "question": "What year was The King of Fighters '95 released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5374387502670288,
            "question": "What is the genre of The King of Fighters '95?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4482952356338501,
            "question": "What are some unique features of The King of Fighters '95 gameplay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36956629157066345,
            "question": "What console was the Neo Geo CD compatible with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The King of Fighters '95 was played on Neo Geo CD.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4239_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some unique features of The King of Fighters '95 gameplay?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4239_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of The King of Fighters '95?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4239_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was The King of Fighters '95 released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4239_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4239_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that The King of Fighters '95 is a game produced by SNK for the Neo Geo arcade and home console, among other platforms including the Neo Geo CD. This suggests that the game was indeed played on Neo Geo CD."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that The King of Fighters '95 was released on the Neo Geo CD, which supports the statement that it was played on Neo Geo CD."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}